hpathy.com 2019-05-22

# Hpathy.com Privacy Policy - Hpathy.com

Your privacy is very important to us. Please contact us from our [Contact Us](https://hpathy.com/contact-hpathy/) page if you have any questions or comments about privacy, or how any information you send us may be used. [Hpathy.com](https://hpathy.com/) has created this statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following text discloses our information gathering practices for this Web site (Homeopathy for Everyone – Hpathy.com), and explains how the information is used, protected, and, in certain limited instances that do not violate your privacy, disseminated.

We never sell personal data and we carry out all processing operations in strict compliance with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) (specifically but not limited to Article 6(1)(b) to (f) and Article 28).

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, personal data means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person; an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier (cookies) etc. (the “Personal Data”).

In this policy, “we”, “us”, “Hpathy”, “Hpathy.com” and “our” refer to _Hpathy Medical Publishers_.

 **Information Provided at Registration  
**  
[Hpathy.com](https://hpathy.com/) pledges to protect the privacy of all of our registered users. The Hpathy.com registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and e-mail address), demographic information (like their ZIP code or age). There is no financial information collected.

We use contact information from the registration form for internal purposes, to send the user news, information about new [Hpathy.com](https://hpathy.com/) site features, services or updates, information about our company, and promotional material or offers from some of our corporate partners. You will be given the opportunity to decline these services at the point of registration, and you may opt-out of receiving future mailings (see the Choice/Opt-out section following).

Demographic and personal health information is used to tailor the visitor’s experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

[Hpathy.com](https://hpathy.com/) will not sell or forward to third parties any individually identifiable personal information, e.g., your e-mail address, name, etc, that you supply during the registration process.

 **IP Address and Cookies**  
Your IP address may be used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. We are using cookies to keep track of your password and to personalize your Web page.

Hpathy uses cookies to process information including standard internet log information, user ID of the visitor if he/she is a registered user, details of the visitor’s behavioral patterns upon visiting our site. This is done to provide you with a better experience, ensuring the security of our website and services, marketing purposes and to facilitate the use of certain functions. Cookies are small data files transferred onto computers or devices by sites for record-keeping purposes and to enhance functionality on our site.

Cookies are stored on your individual device and you have full control over their use. You may deactivate or restrict the transmission of cookies by changing the settings of your web browser. Cookies that are already stored may be deleted at any time by yourself.

If you visit Hpathy.com site with cookies deactivated, you may possibly not be able to use all of the functions of our site to the full extent. You will not be able to opt-out of any cookies or other technologies that are “strictly necessary” for the functioning of our website and services.

 **Links to Other Web Sites  
**This site contains links to other sites. [Hpathy.com](https://hpathy.com/) is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Please read the privacy statements of the link sites that you visit.

 **Public Forums  
**[Hpathy.com](https://hpathy.com/) makes forums, message boards available to our users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information, and you should exercise caution when considering the disclosure of your personal information.

 **Security  
**This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Information provided to the various sections of the [Hpathy.com](https://hpathy.com/) site is password-protected.

 **Choice/Opt-Out  
**[Hpathy.com](https://hpathy.com/) provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us. If you wish to unsubscribe to the Hpathy newsletter, you can also do so within any of the newsletters you receive, or you can [unsubscribe here](https://hpathy.com/unsubscribe-homeopathy-for-everyone/).

You can exercise any of the rights mentioned in this Privacy Policy in your Account and/or by contact with Hpathy’s team: webmaster@hpathy.com. In the event of questions or comments relating to the use of Personal Data you may also contact Hpathy team: webmaster@hpathy.com.

 **Google Ads**

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.  
* Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

 **Other Ads**

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

#### Access and Disclosure to Third Parties

We may share your personal information with our third-party service providers, such as analytical services, payment processors, CRM services and other. These service providers may have access to personal information as needed to perform their functions. Third parties with whom we share your data currently include, but are not limited to, Google, RazorPay, PayPal. We transfer your billing details to payment systems to process payments.

These service providers are carefully selected and meet high data protection and security standards. We only share information with them that is required for the services offered.

 **Notification of Changes  
**If we are going to use your personal identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you via e-mail. You will have a choice as to whether we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post the notice, we will also e-mail users who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.

 **Contacting the Web Site  
**If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, [Click Here to Contact Us](https://hpathy.com/contact-hpathy/)

####  **Contact Details of Data Controller:**

Company: Hpathy Medical Publishers

Legal Address: L6132a, Block 33, Rangoli Gardens, Jaipur 302034, India

Contact email address: webmaster@hpathy.com
